Now that we have defined the problem we're trying to solve,
الآن حيث أننا قد عرَّفنا المشكلة التي نحاول حلها،
gotten familiar with the libraries you want to use and I've broken
واعتدنا التعامل مع المكتبات التي تريدون استخدامها، وبعدما قسَّمتُ
the problem down into smaller pieces, we can begin coding.
المشكلة إلى أجزاء أصغر، يمكننا البدء بالتكويد.
There's another benefit to all this planning,
هناك فائدة أخرى لكل هذا التخطيط،
because we have defined the different pieces of our program,
لأننا قد عرَّفنا الأجزاء المختلفة من برنامجنا
we can split up the work between us.
وبالتالي يمكننا تقسيم العمل فيما بيننا.
Since there's two of us, I think it makes sense to split the work into two major pieces.
وحيث أن هناك اثنين منا، أعتقد أن هذا يجعل تقسيم العمل إلى قسمين رئيسيين أمرًا منطقيًا.
Yeah. I'll work on writing the main loop.
نعم. سأعمل على كتابة الحلقة الرئيسية.
This part of the code will manage the article_chain,
سيتحكم هذا الجزء من الكود في article_chain،
limits how quickly we make requests,
ليحدد مدى السرعة التي ننشئ بها طلبات
and print the output of the crawl.
ونطبع بها مخرَج التتبع.
And I'll write the code that actually makes the requests and finds the links.
كما سأكتب الكود الذي ينشئ الطلبات ويعثر على الروابط فعليًا.
Defining each piece will help us to collaborate,
سيساعدنا تعريف كل جزء في التعاون سويًا؛
but we might need to be flexible if things happen that we weren't expecting.
لكننا ربما نحتاج أن نتسم بالمرونة إذا حدثت أشياء لم نكن نتوقعها.
I'll get started with the continue_crawl function.
سأبدأ بالدالة continue_crawl.